Youtube subtitles download by mo.dbxdb.com
when a character motion is given
authoring Garman animation for the
character is one of the fundamental
steps in a computer animation industry a
traditional workflow for doing this is
time and labor consuming the designer is
asked to insert keyframes by manually
editing the mesh with predefined
controllers the keyframes are inserted
densely and will be connected via linear
interpolation for animation
in a traditional workflow it takes more
than 40 hours for an expert to compose a
gamma animation with 400 frames
with our proposed workflow these tacks
can be finished within five minutes here
we show our workflow with the Maya
plugin we developed for our system first
we load a body motion of the character
here we preview the body motion
now we insert one keyframe we first
select the location of the keyframe
select a candidate garment shape predict
in transect parameters and propagate to
the whole sequence for more technical
details please refer to our paper now we
check the result of our gamma animation
prediction we can continue to insert new
keyframes for example for frame 1 7 and
and 75 we are not satisfied with the
current garment prediction we may mark
it as a keyframe and select a new
Kennedy from the data set we may
continue this until the animation
sequence is satisfactory
we may also delayed a keyframe if we
don't want it any more in a continue to
insert new keyframes if necessary
here we show our final garment animation
result
once the garmin animation is created our
system can update it automatically
whence the underlying body motion has
been changed here we added about emotion
and a garmin animation is updated
accordingly here first show the
animation without updating it has
significant artifact as the gamma motion
is not aligned with the new body motion
now we update a gamma animation the new
Garmin is moving naturally according the
body motion why the previous designs are
kept without any further menu effort
here we visualized a garment change
during the editing process by comparing
SI by Sai here on the left is to input
body motion on the right we have a
keyframe inserted at the beginning
marked as a red on the timeline the
Leighton parameters I learned from that
keyframe and are used to generate
garment shape for other frames when
inserting a new keyframe we see that a
gamma shape is the same at the beginning
and changing smoothly towards the second
key free
now the video is paused at the second
keyframe to see the difference between
the left and right the change happens
since we have learned a new latent
parameter for the second keyframe and
interpolate the parameter in the latent
space the new latent parameter will be
used for the rest of animation
it is similar when inserting more
keyframes
you
here we show the result when updating
about emotion the yellow region on the
timeline marks where the body motion has
been changed now on a ride only the body
motion has been changed
now the gamma motion has also been
updated or Prada Li
you
instead of selecting a caddy for
keyframe our system also supports Dirac
shape editing when inserting a new
keyframe
here we come here to Gama che between
the first before editing the second mesh
editing and the third projecting the
Edit mesh into our Laden space and
projected back into 3d space using on a
trend Network the second row shows the
mesh quality we show the animation
before and after the editing side by
side the two animation star at the same
keyframe and at the same keyframe but
the frame at the midpoint has been
changed and marked as a keyframe here we
show another example in this case the
menu editing creates a lot of artifacts
on a gamma shape so the Edit mesh is far
from what we have in a training data set
our approach captures the trend of this
editing but has some artifacts such as
self intersection when projecting it
back to the 3d shape space
here we show more examples with
different garments and different
characters we show a side-by-side
comparison of two animations starting
from the say keyframe but ending with
two different keyframes
you
here we come here a sequence of ground
true simulation in our data set and a
reconstruction through our learned
latent space
you
since our system is only driving by a
fixed period of previous body motion one
application is to create garment
movement for Lube animation
thank you for watching
Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com